Guide to the Cannon Mills Records, 1836-1983 RL.00187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Cannon Mills records
1836-1983
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Cannon Mills Company
RL.00187
160 Linear Feet
Approximately 63,000 items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Biographical Note
Missing Title
1836-1861 Cannon family associated with Concord Steam Manufacturing Co., Concord, N.C.
1852 James William Cannon born in Mecklenburg County, N.C.
1886 J. W. Cannon elected director of Odell Manufacturing Co., Concord, N.C.
1868 J. W. Cannon joined mercantile firm of Cannon, Fetzer, and Wadsworth, Concord, N.C.
1887 J. W. Cannon founded Concord Manufacturing Co.
1892 Charles Albert Cannon born, Concord, N.C.
1893 Cabarrus Cotton Mills founded at Concord, N.C., by J. W. Cannon and others.
1893 Patterson Manufacturing Co. founded at China Grove, Rowan Co., N.C., by J. Frank Patterson, J. W. Cannon, and others.
1895 Kesler Manufacturing Co. founded at Salisbury, N.C.
1898 Cannon production shifted from cloth to towels.
1898 Wiscassett Mills Company founded at Albemarle, Stanly County, N.C., by J. W. Cannon and D. F. Cannon.
1899 Windemere Knitting Mills established at Albemarle, Stanly County, N.C.
1899 Gibson Manufacturing Co. founded at Concord, N.C., by Cannons and others.
1903 Bloomfield Manufacturing Co. founded in 1903 at Statesville, N.C.
1903 Windemere Knitting Mills became part of Wiscassett Mills Co.
1906 Franklin Cotton Mills established at Concord, N.C., by members of the Cannon family.
1907 Barringer Manufacturing Company founded.
1908 Cannon Manufacturing Company began production at Kannapolis, N.C.
1909 Imperial Cotton Mills founded at Eatonton, Georgia, by J. W. Cannon.
1911 Buck Creek Cotton Mills founded at Siluria, Ala.
1913 York Cotton Mills, York, S.C., purchased.
1915 Norcott Mills Co. established at Concord, N.C., with the Cannons and the Southern Power Co. among the early stockholders.
ca. 1915 Social Circle Cotton Mill Co., Walton County, Georgia, acquired by the Cannons.
1921 J. W. Cannon died. Charles Albert Cannon became company president.
1923 Hobarton Manufacturing Co. founded at Concord, N.C., by Charles A. Cannon and others.
1923 Swink Manufacturing Co., Rowan Co., N.C., incorporated.
1928 Cannon Mills formed from consolidation of Cannon Manufacturing Co., Cabarrus Cotton Mills, Barringer Manufacturing Co., Franklin Cotton mills, Gibson Manufacturing Co., Kesler Manufacturing Co., Patterson Manufacturing Co., Norcott Mills., and Hobarton Manufacturing Co.
ca. 1928 Bloomfield Manufacturing Co., Statesville, N.C., acquired by Cannon Mills.
1931 Swink Manufacturing Company dissolved and assets taken over by Cannon and Swink.
1935 Issaqueena Mill, Central, S.C., purchased and became Central Mills.
1935 Bloomfield Manufacturing Co. sold to J. W. Abernethy.
ca. 1944-1945 Plant at York, S.C., combined with Central Mills.
1947 Brown-Roberta Foundation established at Concord, N.C.
1949 Travora Textiles at Graham and Haw River, N.C., incorporated.
1956 Brown Manufacturing Co., Concord, N.C., acquired by Cannon Mills.
1956 Roberta Manufacturing Co., Cabarrus County, N.C., acquired.
1957 Central Mills closed.
1967 Travora Textiles at Graham and Haw River, N.C., liquidated.
ca 1970-1971 Brown Manufacturing Co., Concord, N.C., closed.
1971 Charles Albert Cannon died.
1971 Don S. Holt became president.
1974 Harold P. Hornaday became president.
1976 Imperial Cotton Mills at Eatonton, Georgia closed.
1978 Roberta Manufacturing Co. liquidated.
1979 Otto G. Stolz became president.
1982 David H. Murdock, purchased Cannon Mills.
1983 Social Circle Cotton Mill Co., Walton County, Georgia, liquidated.
1985-1986 Fieldcrest, Inc. purchased bath and bedding operations of Cannon Mills, and Fieldcrest-Cannon was established.
Collection Overview
The Cannon Mills Records, a textile manufacturer, span the years 1836-1983, although the bulk occurs during 1887-1983. Files and account books concern the operations of Cannon Manufacturing Company and its successor in 1928, Cannon Mills, its subsidiary and associated textile mills, related business interests, and community involvement. The records include correspondence, volumes, memoranda, statistical compilations, reports, printed material, and financial and legal documents.
In 1898 Cannon Manufacturing Company switched to towel manufacturing, and in later years the product line expanded into blankets. In 1971 sales exceeded $305 million, and the company dominated over 50% of the country's towel business and over 20% of the sheet business.
Important topics include the textile industry, economic conditions related to the textile industry, textile marketing and sales, state and national textile industry associations and public and governmental relations; textile industry consolidation; textile equipment and manufacturers; textile production and costs; an antebellum textile mill; and the Cannon, Patterson, Swink, Odell, Barringer, Johnston, Murdoch, and other families who were owners and managers of one or more of the textile mills.
Topics and materials related to personnel are millworkers (both men and women), child labor (both girls and boys), employee retirement plans, the Textile Workers Union of America, time books, employee injuries, company mercantile stores, and mill houses and villages.
Other business activities involved building construction, architects, and contractors; investment in securities and commodities; advertising; taxation; stock and stockholders (both men and women); corporate directors; insurance; bankruptcy and bad debts; cotton brokers; cotton buying and the cotton market; dividends; banks and banking; mill superintendents' records; real estate; lawsuits, one involving racial discrimination; and estate settlements.
Community relations are evident in records relating to churches, schools, the Y.M.C.A., Freemasons, philanthropy to local organizations, and secondary boarding schools in North Carolina and the inception of agricultural training for boys and home economics for girls. The city of Kannapolis, N.C., in which the main offices of Cannon were located, was a particular focus of company interest.
There are record series for the nine companies that were consolidated in 1928 to form Cannon Mills: Cannon Manufacturing Company, Cabarrus Cotton Mills, Barringer Manufacturing Company, Franklin Cotton Mills, Gibson Manufacturing Company, Kesler Manufacturing Company, Patterson Manufacturing Company, Norcott Mills Company, and Hobarton Manufacturing Company. These mills were all in the western Piedmont of North Carolina.
A number of other mills, owned by or associated with the Cannons or Cannon Mills, had a separate existence in North Carolina, South Carolina, Georgia and Alabama. Those mills, represented in this collection by series, include Central Mills, Central, S.C.; Bloomfield Manufacturing Co., Statesville, N.C.; Brown Manufacturing Co., Concord, N.C.; Roberta Manufacturing Co., Cabarrus County, N.C.; Imperial Cotton Mills, Eatonton, Georgia; Social Circle Cotton Mills, Walton County, Georgia, Swink Manufacturing Company, Rowan County, N.C.; Travora Textiles, Graham and Haw River, N.C.; Windemere Knitting Mills, Albemarle, N.C.; and Wiscassett Mills, Albemarle, N.C. Other mills, not represented here by series, were related to the Cannon group, and information about them occasionally appears in the collection. These firms include: Amazon Cotton Mills, Thomasville, N.C.; Durham Hosiery Mills; Efird Manufacturing Co., Albemarle, N.C.; Tuscarora Cotton Mill, Mt. Pleasant, N.C.; Buck Creek Cotton Mills, Siluria, Ala.; and Paola Cotton Mills, Statesville, N.C.
Basic information about these textile mills can be found in the annual volumes of Davidson's Textile Blue Book. The size and products of many of the factories varied over the years.
The huge Cannon corporation also had related business interests and community involvements that are represented by organizations and record series in this collection. They include: Cannon Mills, Inc., the selling agency in New York City; Cannon of West Coast, Inc.; L. T. Barringer and Co., a cotton brokerage firm in Memphis, Tennessee; the Brown-Roberta Foundation, a community philanthropy; J. A. Skipwith and Co., cotton brokers at Concord, N.C.; Klumac Cotton Mills, Salisbury, N.C.; P. M. Morris Real Estate Company, Concord, N.C.; Rowan County Farm Life School; and the Trading and Commission Company, a selling agency and holding company.
The series in this collection represent executives, offices, a department, subsidiary companies, affiliated companies, and related businesses and organizations. The general arrangement of the 47 series is: reference information; members of the Cannon family; executive offices; executives; a department; and numerous companies, businesses, and organizations, these arranged mostly alphabetically.
The surviving files and volumes represent only a small percentage of the original archives. Some parts of the company have considerable papers in this collection, but no series is anywhere near complete. Some series are quite small. Record survival was random, but many important and useful files and account books are available.
Information about particular topics, companies, and individuals is often scattered in a number of series in this collection, and the container list serves as a guide to many of them. It should be remembered that company activities may be reflected by bookkeeping entries in the account books whether or not relevant files are available. Because of the interlocking relationships of the various companies, information about one firm may not be exclusive to its own series.
Freemasonry -- North Carolina; Decedents' estates -- North Carolina; Industries -- North Carolina; Industrial life insurance; Industries -- Georgia; Stock ownership; Real estate business -- North Carolina; Textile industry; Investments; Textile workers -- Southern States; Industries -- Alabama; Cotton trade; Banks and banking; Agricultural education -- North Carolina; Corporations -- Charitable contributions -- North Carolina; Kannapolis (N.C.) -- Commerce; New York (N.Y.) -- Commerce; Tennessee -- Commerce; Labor and laboring classes -- Southern States; Construction industry -- Southern States; Corporations -- Public relations; Home economics, Rural -- North Carolina; South Carolina -- Industries; United States -- Economic conditions; Young Men's Christian Association of Kannapolis, N.C.; Cannon, James William, 1852-1921; Cannon, Charles Albert, 1892-1971
- Information Series
  Scope and Contents note
  Reference material including histories, historical articles, biographical sketches of the Cannons, and data on some of the textile mills.
  - Histories and Historical Articles (Box 1)
  - Historical Data and Views (Box 1)
  - Biographical material (Box 1)
  - Company Information from Davison's Textile Blue Book (Box 1)
  - Company Information from Moody's Manual of Investments (Box 1)
- James William Cannon Series, 1887-1937, bulk 1907-1922
  Correspondence, memoranda, legal and financial papers, reports, and volumes centering upon the founder of Cannon Mills. Important files relating to mill operations concern the early years of Buck Creek Cotton Mills at Siluria, Ala., and Cannon's management of Paola Cotton Mills at Statesville, N.C. There is considerable financial data and some correspondence for the New York office. A record book contains early production, cost, labor and other statistics. Overseer Joseph D. Bacon's reminiscences provide a vignette of J. W. Cannon's early years in management. T. C. Thompson, a builder and contractor, was associated with Cannon in Buck Creek Cotton Mills.
  Information about J. W. Cannon's finances and personal investments is extensive. It includes his dealing with H. Hentz and Co., J. S. Bache and Co., and the Farmers' Loan and Trust Co. of New York City. Trading in securities and commodities was considerable. There is also some record of other ventures such as real estate and oil production.
  Papers relating to Cannon and his family include wills, estate records, and financial documents and accounts. Files for the settlement of the estate of Mrs. Cannon's uncle, Aaron J. Bost, are extensive, and securities investments are itemized.
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - Amazon Cotton Mills: (Box 2)
      - List of Stockholders, ca. 1919-1920 (Box 2)
    - Bacon, Joseph D.:
      - Reminiscences of James W. Cannon and Origin and Development of Cannon Manufacturing Co. by Overseer Joseph D. Bacon, 1937 (Box 2)
    - Buck Creek Cotton Mills (Siluria, Ala.):
      - 1911, 1916-1917 (Box 2)
      - 1918-1920 (Box 2)
      - 1921, 1930, and undated (Box 2)
      - Audit Report for 1920, Oct. 1-1921, March 31 (Box 2)
    - Cannon, James William:
      - Biographical Sketch for National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 1922 (Box 2)
      - Tributes at Death, 1921-1922 (Box 2)
      - Will and Estate, 1921-1922 (Box 2)
    - Cannon, James William, Jr.:
      - Will, 1914 (Box 2)
    - Cannon, Mary Ella (Mrs. J. W. Cannon):
      - Investment in the William R. Hande System Woman's Posture and Figure Mold Association, 1927-1928 (Box 2)
      - Trust Agreement with Cabarrus Bank and Trust Co, 1934 (Box 2)
      - Will and Codicils, 1923-1926 (Box 2)
    - Cannon, McGill, and Webb:
      - Account Book for Real Estate, 1897-1924, Including Records, 1896-1909, for Other Real Estate, Medical Receipts, etc., for J. W. Cannon (Box 2)
      - Financial Papers, 1898-1923 (Box 2)
    - Cannon and Company, York, S.C., Account, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
    - Cannon Family Genealogy (Box 2)
    - Cannon Mills, New York:
      - Financial Statement, 1910, July-Dec. (Box 2)
      - Financial Statements, 1913, Jan-June, (Including Philadelphia Office) (Box 2)
    - Cannon Mills, New York: (Box 3)
      - Financial Statements, 1913, July- 1913, Dec. (Including Philadelphia Office), 3 folders (Box 3)
      - Financial Statements, 1915-1919 (Box 3)
      - Outside Yarn and Cloth Commissions, 1913-1914 (Box 3)
    - Checkbook Stubs:
      - 1915-1917 (2 vols.) (Box 3)
    - Chemical National Bank, New York City, 1919 (Box 3)
    - Child Labor Legislation, ca. 1916 (Box 3)
    - Coal Report, 1918 (Box 3)
    - Contract File, 1914-1922, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Correspondence:
      - 1888-1915 (Box 3)
      - 1916: C, M, P, W, 4 folders (Box 3)
      - 1917: C, M, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Correspondence: (Box 4)
      - 1917: P, S, W, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - 1918: C, M, P, W, 4 folders (Box 4)
      - 1919: C, M, P, W, 4 folders (Box 4)
      - 1919-1921 and undated (Box 4)
    - Estate of Aaron J. Bost (Uncle of Mrs. J. W. Cannon):
      - Will, 1916 (Box 4)
      - Appraisal, 1919 (Box 4)
      - Cashbook, 1919-1921 (Box 4)
      - Cashbook for Stocks and Bonds, 1920-1921 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1918-1921 and undated (Box 4)
    - Estate of Aaron J. Bost (Uncle of Mrs. J. W. Cannon): (Box 5)
      - Final Account and Settlement, 1921 (Box 5)
      - Financial Papers and Memoranda, 1918-1922 and undated, 3 folders (Box 5)
      - Ledger, 1920-1921 (Box 5)
      - Ledger of Farm Sales, 1920-1921 (Box 5)
      - Ledger of Stock Sales, 1920-1921, and Related Correspondence, 1919-1921 (Box 5)
      - Taxes, 1920-1922 (Box 5)
    - Efird Manufacturing Company:
      - Financial Statement, 1916, and List of Stockholders, 1919 (Box 5)
    - Estate of James William Cannon, 1922 (Box 5)
    - Farmers' Loan and Trust Company, New York City, 1917, July-Dec. (Box 5)
    - Farmers' Loan and Trust Company, New York City: (Box 6)
      - 1918, Jan.-1919, Sept., 7 folders (Box 6)
      - 1919, Oct.-1920, Jan. 1920; 1921, Jan.; and undated (Box 6)
      - Accounts, 1917-1921 (Box 6)
    - Financial Papers (Miscellaneous):
      - 1900-1921 and undated (Box 6)
    - H. Hentz and Co., New York City: (Box 7)
      - 1907-1909 (Box 7)
      - 1910-1915 (Box 7)
      - 1916, Jan..-Dec., 1916, 4 folders (Box 7)
      - 1917, Jan.-1917, Dec., 3 folders (Box 7)
      - 1918, Jan.-Nov., 1918, 1919-1921, and undated, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Investment Memoranda, 1913-1914 (Box 8)
    - Investment Record Book and Memoranda, 1899-1908 (Box 8)
    - Investment Record Book and Income Memoranda, 1908- 1917 (bulk, 1913-1914) (Box 8)
    - Investment Record Book, 1917-1919 (Box 8)
    - J. S. Bache and Co., New York City:
      - 1916 (Box 8)
      - 1917, Jan.-Dec. (Box 8)
      - 1918 (Box 8)
      - 1919-1921 (Box 8)
    - Legal Papers: Miscellaneous, 1892-1911 (Box 8)
    - Life Insurance, 1908 (Box 8)
    - Life Insurance Policies, 1887-1904, and Stock with H. Hentz and Co., 1907 (Box 8)
    - Memorandum Book, ca. 1920-1921 (Box 9)
    - Mill House and Other Buildings Construction by Jno. R. Query, Contractor and Builder:
      - 1911-1912 (Box 9)
      - 1913, May-1913, Oct., 2 folders (Box 9)
      - 1913-1914 and undated (Box 9)
      - Ledger, 1912-1914 (Box 9)
    - New York Office Correspondence:
      - 1916 (Box 9)
      - 1917, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 9)
      - 1918, Jan.-Dec., 2 folders (Box 9)
      - 1919 (Box 9)
    - Notes Payable, 1900-1906 (Box 9)
    - Office Fixtures and Furniture, ca. 1918 (Box 10)
    - Oil Industry Development, 1919-1920 (Box 10)
    - Paola Cotton Mills (Statesville, N.C.):
      - Correspondence, 1915, June-1918 Apr., 4 folders (Box 10)
      - Invoices, 1915-1916 (Box 10)
    - Post and Flagg Account for Investments of Mary Ella Cannon, 1921 (Box 10)
    - Record Book of Financial Statements and Production, Cost, Labor, and Other Statistics for Mills in Cannon System, 1888-1903 (bulk, 1901-1903) (Box 10)
    - Schafer Bros., Wall St., New York: Investment Accounts, 1915-1916 (Box 10)
    - Southern Power Company, 1907 (Box 10)
    - Stock Increase of 1908 and Subscriptions:
      - Sept., 1908 (Box 10)
      - Oct., 1908 (Box 10)
    - Stock Increase of 1908 and Subscriptions:
      - Nov., 1908-1909 and undated (Box 10)
    - Stonewall Jackson Manual Training and Industrial School, Concord, N.C., 1922 (Box 11)
    - Taxes, 1913-1918 (Box 11)
    - Tiffany and Co., 1919-1920 (Box 11)
    - Tuscarora Cotton Mills, 1908 and undated (Box 11)
- Charles Albert Cannon Series, 1836-1971, bulk 1916-1963
  Correspondence, memoranda, legal and financial papers, reports, and volumes relating to C. A. Cannon, the company's manager from 1921 to 1971. There are notable files for the advertising agencies of Young and Rubicam, N. W. Ayer and Son, and the Market Research Corporation of America. External public relations and industry concerns were expressed through such organizations as the American Cotton Manufacturers Association, American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, National Cotton Council, Textile Committee on Public Relations, and the Committee for a National Trade Policy. Lawsuits between Cannon and the Collector of Internal Revenue and the estate of William A. Stribling, a cotton buying and receiving agent, caused the compilation of considerable information and financial statistics about Cannon Mills and some of its subsidiary and related mills. There are also records from the antebellum Concord Steam Manufacturing Co.; the Odell Manufacturing Co.; Charles Cannon's investments and cash transactions; the securities investments of James W. Cannon and Mary Ella (Bost) Cannon; the estate of Thomas T. Smith, a former secretary of Cannon Manufacturing; the consolidation of 1928; and a lodge of Freemasons at Concord, N.C.
  - Boxed Files and Volumes
    - Advertising: (Box 11)
      - 1941-1944, 4 folders (Box 11)
    - Advertising: (Box 12)
      - 1945 (Box 12)
      - 1946 (Box 12)
      - 1946: Information to Submit to Schools, etc. (Box 12)
      - 1947 (Box 12)
      - 1948 (Box 12)
      - 1949 (Box 12)
      - 1949: N. W. Ayer and Son (Box 12)
      - 1949: Young and Rubicam (Box 12)
      - 1950: Cannon Consumer Education Program (Box 12)
    - Advertising: (Box 13)
      - 1950: N. W. Ayer and Son (Box 13)
      - 1950: Young and Rubicam (Box 13)
      - 1951 (Box 13)
      - 1954 (Box 13)
      - 1955 (Box 13)
      - 1955: Market Research Corporation of America Report (Box 13)
      - 1956: Market Research Corporation of America Reports, Jan.-April (Box 13)
      - 1956: Market Research Corporation of American Reports, May-Nov. (Box 13)
      - 1957: Market Research Corporation of America Reports (Box 13)
    - Allice Manufacturing Company, Easley, S.C., 1955 (Box 14)
    - American Cotton Manufacturers Association:
      - Dr. Jules Backman, 1944-1946 (Box 14)
    - American Cotton Manufacturers Institute:
      - 1953 (Box 14)
      - 1956, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute:
      - Special Cotton Policy Committee, 1958- 1964, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - American Textile Manufacturers Institute: (Box 15)
      - Special Cotton Policy Committee, 1971 and undated (Box 15)
    - Amortization of Machinery and Girls Dormitory:
      - 1917-1923 (Box 15)
      - Crompton and Knowles Loom Works, 1917-1918 (Box 15)
      - Dormitories, 1918-1924 (Box 15)
      - Record of Invoices, 1919-1921 (Box 15)
      - Schedule of Amortized Property by Ernst and Ernst, 1920 (Box 15)
      - Annual Banquet Menu, 1925 (Box 15)
      - Cannon, Laura (Mrs. Charles E. Lambeth), undated (Box 15)
      - Cannon, William Coltrane, 1953 (Box 15)
      - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Concord Steam Manufacturing Company:
      - Minutes (Box 15)
      - 1836-1861 (Typescript) (Box 15)
    - Consolidation of 1928:
      - Agreement of Consolidation (Box 15)
    - Consolidation of 1928: (Box 16)
      - Audit Reports, 1927, by Haskins and Sells (Box 16)
      - Barringer Manufacturing Company, Special Meeting of Stockholders, July 5, 1928 (Box 16)
      - Cabarrus Cotton Mills, Redemption of Preferred Stock (Box 16)
      - Cabarrus Cotton Mills, Special Meeting of Stockholders, 1928, July 5 (Box 16)
      - Cannon Manufacturing Co., Special Meeting of Stockholders, 1928, July 5 (Box 16)
      - Cannon Manufacturing Co., Stockholder Proxies, 1928, July 5, A-Y (6 folders) B (Box 16)
      - Cannon Mills Co., Exchange of Stock of Nine Mills for Its Stock (Box 16)
      - Cannon Mills Co., Redemption of Preferred Stock (Box 16)
      - Deposit Agreement, Purchase Contract, and Related Correspondence (Box 16)
      - Financial Statements, Letters and Printed Material 1927-1928 (Box 16)
      - Gibson Manufacturing Co., Redemption of Preferred Stock (Box 16)
      - Gibson Manufacturing Co., Special Meeting of Stockholders, 1928, July 5 (Box 16)
      - Hobarton Manufacturing Co., Special Meeting of Stockholders, 1928, July 5 (Box 16)
      - Kesler Manufacturing Co., Special Meeting of Stockholders, 1928, July 5 (Box 16)
    - Consolidation of 1928: (Box 17)
      - Norcott Mills Co., Special Meeting of Stockholders, 1928, July 5 (Box 17)
    - Notices in Newspapers (Box 17)
    - Notices to Stockholders (Box 17)
    - Patterson Manufacturing Co., Special Meeting of Stockholders, 1928, July 5 (Box 17)
    - Purchase and Sale of Fractional Shares of Stock (Box 17)
    - Receipts for Stock of Cannon Manufacturing Co. and Authorization for Dividend Payments, 1928, Nos. 2-293 (Box 17)
    - Receipts for Stock of Cannon Manufacturing Co. and Authorization for Dividend Payments, 1928, Nos. 300-651 (Box 17)
    - Stock Dividend and Exchange of Stock of Cabarrus Cotton Mills and Norcott Mills (Box 17)
    - Stock of Mrs. Adelaide Cannon Blair (Mrs. David H. Blair), J. Barnette Douglass, Adelaide C. Douglass, David H. Blair, Jr. (Box 17)
    - Stock of Mrs. Ashlyn L. Cannon (Mrs. J. Ross Cannon), J. W. Cannon, III, and Ashlyn L. Cannon (Box 17)
    - Stock of Charles A. Cannon (Box 17)
    - Stock of Charles A. Cannon, Fractions Bought and Sold, 1928, June-1929, May, 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Consolidation of 1928: (Box 18)